Hilde Dickhaut. Born October 20, 1858.
Died of exsanguination August 17, 1889.
No notes of interest.
That wraps up today's job.
Let's call it a night.
Yes.
Still, to think those two survived
and went to England.
Isn't it amazing how human history
is built on things like this?
You're making too big a deal of it, Sascha.
It's just two humans going to England.
Ah-ah-ah! That's where you're wrong, Ludger.
Just think: an incredibly lethal new gas
and the developer of that gas
are both bound for England.
What a perfect way to keep Germany in check!
Ugh, here we go.
They fought with swords and arrows
until just a few centuries ago,
but now they're making poisons
that can kill hundreds with one drop.
Human progress is amazing.
What's more, there are minor geniuses
like these all over the world.
If just one of them upsets
the world's balance,
it might trigger a great war
that will engulf the whole globe!
That would be rotten.
Personally, I'd rather have a world war
than too much time on my hands.
And I'd wager...
...he feels the same way.
I'm not that kind of freak,
so I'd rather not be so busy.
I quite agree.
If that happened, we'd never
get to leave work on time.
Hi there. You've come a long way...
William and Grell.
Too long.
Yoo-hoo! I've missed you to death!
Black Butler
Emerald Witch Arc
A red coat, eh?
You're as flashy as ever.
But of course! I'm the only lady in the English
branch's Collections Department, after all!
Here's the handover documentation.
I didn't anticipate being sent
all the way to Germany on business.
What a nuisance. The whole world
seems primed for war these days.
Well, even though I'm sad
we missed Sebas-chan,
I had fun on this little trip
with you, Will—ouch!
Speaking of war, how did that affair
with the walking corpses turn out?
It's still under investigation.
I take it none have appeared
here in Germany yet.
Still, please contact the English branch
with any information about the deserter.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
Toodles!
Will, let's make a side trip to Baden-Baden!
There have always been
the occasional job deserters, I guess.
What do you think makes them want to run
from the Grim Reaper Staffing Association?
Never thought about it.
They might just be bored with their jobs,
or they might have some special reason.
Well, I suppose I can understand.
We used to be human, after all.
Humans who commit suicide are turned
into grim reapers as punishment,
then worked to the bone
until the day we're forgiven,
endlessly gazing at death like this.
It's pretty depressing for us suicides
to have to hear people
regretting their deaths and
thirsting for life day in and day out, huh?
You don't look the least bit depressed.
Yep, I'm having more fun now than I did
when I was alive! Maybe it's my divine calling?
Nothing divine about grim reapers.
Welcome back, sir.
You've certainly...
made a lot of mischief.
Heinrich, get a doctor.
And draw a bath, too.
Yes, sir.
It's been a long time since I've seen you.
Indeed it has, my friend!
Who is this?
This is Phantomhive's son.
I knew it!
It's an honour to meet you, Lord Phantomhive.
I appreciate the hospitality.
I can see your father in you.
I apologize for my appearance.
It's so big!
This is one of several castles
held by the Weizsäcker barony.
I'm afraid it's rather small
compared to the main castle,
but please do make yourselves at home.
Small?!
You're a sheltered rich boy, huh?
Says the pot to the kettle.
Let's show our guests to their rooms.
At once.
Please bring the injured man this way.
This way, please.
We'll bring you fresh clothes right away.
Heinrich, allow us to help as well.
Thank you.
The doctor will be here soon.
Please hold on just a little longer.
We're here, and Wolfram seems
to have pulled through. That's a relief.
Yes.
This may sting a bit, but please bear with it.
Pardon me, my lord.
I wonder how much of this
Her Majesty anticipated.
Did she really send us here
to investigate the mysterious deaths?
Or did she expect us to find German
military secrets when she gave those orders?
Who knows? A queen's thoughts are
beyond a mere butler's understanding.
But one thing is clear:
Germany's toxic gas and
tank development is at a high level.
That, and England has also
acquired those same things.
I believe the future
will be very interesting.
All right, close your eyes.
Hmph. "Interesting" isn't the word.
Truly, humans change at dizzying speed.
And yet...
You haven't grown any taller.
Why is that, I wonder?
I'll take none of that from you.
You haven't changed in centuries.
Undertaker?
He was here recently.
What?
What was he doing in Germany?
He said he had business in France
and decided to stop by.
I had no idea he was involved
in the sinking of that luxury liner.
France?
Do you have any idea where he is?
No, I don't.
But...
I haven't seen you in a long time, Diederich.
Not since his funeral, I think.
You don't come to England much anymore.
Is that because the earl is gone?
Or because your body is harder to mov—
I couldn't hold it in!
What the devil are you here for?!
It's just that you've changed so much.
Humans do change in
such little time, don't they?
You used to be so thin.
Leave it out.
We'll probably have to
special order your coffin.
Shall I measure you now, just in case?
Not necessary.
The earl would probably laugh
if he could see you now.
I don't even want to picture it.
He did me a favour by dying fir—
Poor thing. Burned down to his bones.
No coming back from a death like that.
Oh, but...
There's still the other
Earl Phantomhive, after all.
He said "the other"?
I paid it no mind at the time,
since he always talks nonsense, but...
Did he mean me?
Or...
Sir, dinner is ready. Shall I bring it in here?
No, we'll move to the dining room.
What will you lot do next?
My job will be done once
I've handed Sullivan over to the Queen.
We'll return to England as soon
as the injured man can move.
Ah, Ciel!
I started without you,
and everything is delicious.
You should hurry up and eat, too.
Seconds, please!
R-Right away, yes!
I fear she's not quite ready
for tea with the Queen, my lord.
I'm well aware.
Then, we'll have to make sure she's strictly
trained in ladylike manners once we get home.
I look forward to the challenge.
I'll entrust you with the task.
Her Majesty is eagerly waiting,
so make short work of it.
Very good.
His resilience is truly marvellous.
He's strong. He'll be up and about in no time.
Your name is Sebastian, yes?
Why did you save me?
My young master ordered me to.
It was very irresponsible of you
to decide your work was done,
and leave us to mind her.
Y-Young mistress, I...
Say no more.
I betrayed you first.
That night, I jumped at their promise
to show me the outside world,
and I decided to leave the forest.
I let my desires take over,
and I was going to abandon you all.
But you protected me anyway.
Yes, I'm angry with you
for deceiving me all this time.
But I did something cruel, too.
So...
Let's say we're even.
Young mistress...
You... forgive me?
Does this mean I can remain your butler?
Yes. Let's stay together forever.
Let's see the outside world
together, Wolfram.
Ja.
They suit you!
Just bear with it until we get to England, yes.
We owe you, Diederich.
You certainly do. Like father, like son.
Next time, don't bring trouble to my door.
"Next time"? So we're welcome to come again?
D-Don't look at me like that.
And don't come back. Good riddance to you.
Junior.
The times are about to change radically.
Be careful.
Same to you.
So this is London!
This is the capital of the land where
"the sun never sets," ruled by Queen Victoria.
Oi, you two.
German is too conspicuous in Great Britain.
Please speak English from now on.
Right.
What?
The young mistress may manage,
but I can hardly speak a word!
Then, as much as possible, please.
I'll give you close instruction
once we're back at the manor.
I imagine the Queen is impatient to see her.
I'd like to introduce them in a week.
A week? Isn't that a bit too soon?
I know you can get her to pass muster
by then. I'll leave the methods to you.
Look! What's that?
This is an order, Sebastian:
Turn this unruly girl
into a lady within one week.
Yes, my lord.
First things first: her attire.
See you soon!
Presentations to Her Majesty
have a strict dress code.
Let's commission her full court dress.
Hello.
Welcome to Hopkins.
Their poses get no less strange.
It's good to see you again.
We'd like to order several items.
I sense a beautiful boy has entered!
Meg, Augusta, who is it?
You have keen senses, Miss Hopkins.
Oh!
Goodness, my lord. How good it is to see you!
You so rarely come to my establishment!
I always admire the thoroughness
with which you ignore me.
And who might this lady be, my lord?
A guest. I'll be taking her in for a while.
Her wardrobe is bare, so I'd like
some dresses for her. Off the rail is fine.
Ah, yes, I can see this dress
isn't made of proper summer fabric.
And these colours are much too plain.
To say nothing of the poor workmanship.
A stuffy, outdated man who thinks "women should
be ladylike" clearly foisted his tastes on you.
I was coping with a crisis.
Pardon?
These two need to be outfitted for
her presentation to the Queen at a Drawing Room.
Ordinarily, we would order the lady's
full court dress from a couturiere,
but may I venture to ask you
for her costume along with his?
A ridiculous question.
A debutante's presentation...
Cheeks rosy with nervous excitement...
It's good. Too good!
I have it! The fount of
my imagination is overflowing!
The rules state that a presentation dress
should be pristine white.
She'll need a long silk petticoat
with plenty of lace.
Perhaps embroidered satin for the train?
We'll make her hair look festive
with feathers and a veil.
And an emerald or diamond accessory
would be just the thing!
Right! Step this way, please.
Meg, Augusta, take that one's measurements.
She remains very...
...true to herself.
Sorry about the mess, dear.
I'm working on a large order
for a choir right now.
Now, what colours shall I pick
for your everyday dresses?
I have plenty of things to hand.
I'd like to ask a favour.
That should take care of the attire.
A lady being presented must have
her hair coiffed as befits the upper class.
Fortunately, Fräulein Sullivan already has
nice long hair, so it shouldn't be an issue.
Next up—
Here I am.
Young mistress?!
Ciel, you're finally home.
I look forward to this!